And here's another
interesting weather fact.
Another? Great!
Changes in jet streams
can affect the speed
at which the Earth
rotates on its axis,
so bad weather can actually
make the day longer.
Well, there must be a hell
of a storm somewhere.
Joke if you must, but you're
going to miss these moments.
With Leonard home in a few days,
this was your last time
driving me to the grocery store.
You know, I will miss this.
I'll tell you what,
if my apples are mealy,
we'll hit the produce section
for one last crazy blowout.
Heck, you can even push the cart.
Please don't take my looking
forward to Leonard's return
as criticism of the job you've
been doing in his absence.
I won't.
That criticism will come later
in your report card.
Yeah, I didn't stay
for the detention,
I'm not gonna read
the report card.
-Hello.
-(SCREAMS) Leonard! Hi!
-Sh! Keep your voice down.
-Oh, my God. You weren't supposed
-to be here till Sunday!
-We finished the experiment early,
so I thought I'd come home
and surprise you.
Oh, my gosh,
why are we whispering?
I didn't tell Sheldon
so we could have a few days alone.
-Oh! That is so romantic.
-Sure, that's why I did it.
I just cannot believe you're here.
SHELDON: Penny, it's your lucky day!
Three of the eggs are clearly
not jumbo. Grab your keys.
J (THEME SONG PLAYING) &
Stuart, I was wondering
if you could help me find something.
Happy to, unless it's hope
or a reason to live.
Oh, you make me laugh, sad clown.
Anyhoo, Leonard will be back
in a couple days
and I need a welcome-home
gift for him.
As he's been at sea,
perhaps something
with a nautical theme
might be appropriate.
Okay, well, I don't know
how much you want to spend,
but I do have this pretty
cool Aquaman statue.
Aquaman?
This isn't a gag gift, Stuart.
Yeah, just as well.
It's a pretty rare piece.
I'd rather just sell it
to a real collector.
I'm a real collector.
How rare is it?
I shouldn't even have mentioned it.
How about a Batman squirt gun?
Ye--
Don't try and trick me
into buying something I don't want.
Now, let's talk Aquaman.
What were they thinking,
putting Doctor Octopus's mind
in Spider-Man's body?
Well, I've been quite enjoying that.
It combines all the
superhero fun of Spider-Man
with all the body-switching
shenanigans of Freaky Friday.
Both versions: original and Lohan.
(INDIAN ACCENT) "Both versions:
original and Lohan." You're an idiot.
Hey, what's your problem?
I'm sorry.
I've been kind of snippy lately.
It's probably this stupid diet
I'm on.
-Why are you on a diet?
-I've put on a couple pounds.
Had to buy these pants
in the men's section.
Well, we've all seen your mom.
That Butterball turkey
was bound to come home to roost.
Twelve-hundred dollars!
That's my final offer!
All right, Sheldon, you win.
I'm sure Leonard
is gonna love this.
Oh, right, a present for Leonard.
You better throw in that squirt gun.
Hm... Yeah, I don't know.
This squirt gun, it's... it's pretty rare.
Oh!
And this is me doing
the Titanic pose on the boat.
Oh!
And... oh, that's me getting rescued
after I fell in.
Oh.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
-Oh. That's the pizza.
-Yep.
-Here's some money.
-Thank you.
And I'm gonna hit the head.
That's what us salty sea dogs say
when we have to go pee-pee.
-Hey.
-Twenty-two, fifty.
Okay, here's 25.
Keep the change.
Seriously? I just walked up,
like, four flights of stairs.
Oh, okay. Well, here's, um...
Thirty-something cents,
and a promise
I won't call your boss
and tell him
you reek of marijuana.
Oh, Penny, I see
you've ordered pizza.
-I have Chinese food.
-That's nice.
Oh, that's a rather earthy cologne.
My uncle used to wear that.
Perhaps we can enjoy one last meal
together before Leonard returns.
Yeah, thanks, but I kind of feel
like eating alone tonight, so--
Are you sure? With your Italian pizza
and my Chinese noodles,
we could play Marco Polo.
I mean, of course,
a reenactment of a meal
in the life of Marco Polo
the Venetian explorer,
not Marco Polo
the terrifying water sport.
Uh, yeah. It sounds fun,
but no thanks.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
Have a good night!
-What, now, do you have company?
-No. No, no, no.
You know what?
The toilet's been doing that.
-I called the building manager, so--
-Oh, I can take a look at it.
-Well--
-I'm quite familiar with plumbing.
Not to brag, but I spent most of
fifth grade with my head in a toilet.
Yeah, no, no, no.
You know what, Sheldon, it's okay.
You don't have to go
into the bathroom.
That's curious.
If there's no one here,
why are there two glasses
of wine on the table?
Oh. Well, you know,
I've got two hands
and a bit of a drinking problem.
Of course.
Ask a silly question.
-That's odd.
-What?
There are takeout containers
in the trash can.
So? That's my dinner from last night.
What's odd is they're
in the trash can.
Okay. Look, honey,
I promise there's no one's here.
I've had a long day. I just want
to have a quiet dinner by myself.
Oh, very well.
I'm no stranger to enjoying
the pleasures of solitude.
-Oh!
-What?
Have you gotten Leonard
a welcome-home gift yet?
-No.
-Oh, great.
Do you want to go halfsies
on a 200 dollar squirt gun?
-Hi, honey.
-Hey.
I made some brownies.
You want one?
You're kidding, right?
I mean, you know
I'm trying to lose weight.
God, I thought we were partners
in this marriage.
We are. Stop it. And for the
last time, you're not fat.
Really? Tell that
to the bathroom scale,
‘cause one of you is lying.
Fine, forget I asked.
How was dinner at your mom's?
Awful. I had to rub her ointment
all over her again.
Why can't she do it?
'‘Cause we've got a deeply
unhealthy relationship.
Which reminds me,
do you think you can get
any samples of this from work?
This was supposed
to last her a month,
but they didn't take into account
the square footage of her back.
Let me see.
How long have you been
putting this on her?
I don't know.
Few weeks. Why?
This is really strong estrogen cream.
Please tell me
you've been wearing gloves.
Like these swollen sausages
could fit in gloves.
Howie, the estrogen's
getting absorbed by your skin.
That's why you've been
all bloated and moody
and a giant pain in the ass.
You're full of estrogen
and you don't act like that.
That's 'cause I'm a woman. I've had
years of practice riding the dragon.
Fine. I'll wear gloves next time.
It's still gonna take a few weeks for
the hormones to leave your system.
I feel so stupid. And fat.
It's okay.
You still look great to me.
In fact, why don't we go in the
bedroom and I'll prove it to you?
Sex? Really? I mean,
that's just your solution to everything!
Oh, and here's a fun thing.
I worked it out so that there are
two different words for spoon:
"planko" and "janko."
"Planko" is a spoon with food,
"janko" is a spoon without food.
"Janko" is spelled
with a silent "ptang."
Sheldon, you're not even listening
to the rules of my made-up language.
-Yes, I am.
-Then what does "tweepadock" mean?
Uh...
Elephant?
Lucky guess.
I'm sorry.
I'm just distracted by something
that happened over at Penny's.
What happened?
I fear Penny is being unfaithful
to Leonard.
-What?
-She claimed to be alone
when there was obviously
someone else in her apartment.
I have no choice but
to assume the worst,
given Leonard's lengthy sea voyage
and her famously
ravenous nether regions.
I don't think Penny
would cheat on Leonard.
Oh, really?
(LAUGHS)
She and I once had
a staring contest.
She clapped really loud
and made me blink.
It's a small leap from there
to sexual infidelity.
You're being ridiculous.
Amy, there were Chinese
food containers... in the trash can.
Poor Leonard.
-Do you hear anything?
- I hear a woman's voice.
-Is it Penny?
-No, it's you.
All right,
I hear whispering and giggling.
Now I think I hear kissing.
Yeah, like you know
what kissing sounds like.
There's kissing in Star Trek,
smarty-pants.
Let me listen.
-Sounds like Leonard.
-Please.
Why would Leonard come home early
and waste his time kissing Penny
when he could be hanging out
with his best buddy?
Yeah, that's it.
I'm catching her in the act.
No, Sheldon, don't.
A-ha!
-What the hell?!
-Leonard?
Sheldon, you cannot just
barge in here like that!
Right.
(KNOCKING LOUDLY)
SHELDON: Penny! Penny! Penny!
Are you going to answer the door
or should I open it
and say "a-ha" again?
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
I should've told you I was back.
I just wanted to have
a couple days alone with Penny.
Oh, no, I should apologize.
I never realized to what extent
our friendship was a burden to you.
That is not fair.
I complain about what a burden it is
at least once a month.
Oh, no, no, let's not sugarcoat this.
You find me finicky,
pedantic and annoying.
No, he doesn't.
I actually have used
those exact words before.
In that order.
Well, Leonard,
I think it's high time
you and I address
the "tweepadock" in the room.
-The what?
-Amy?
-Please leave me out of this.
-Fine.
Leonard, there's no need for you
to pretend to like me anymore.
-Come on, I said I was sorry.
-No, no, you save your apologies
for after you've had
disappointing coitus with Penny.
It was fine.
Come on, this is silly.
Hey, I brought you back
a little present from my trip, huh?
It's that sailor cap that you wanted.
It's neat, huh?
You honestly think you can buy back
my friendship with a cheap souvenir?
I don't. No, I really don't.
Just try it on.
-Oh, yeah.
-Hello, sailor.
Now we're talking.
Excuse me.
This changes nothing.
Except the Halloween costume
I'm wearing this year.
Amy, you're going to be Olive Oyl.
Lay off the donuts.
-Thanks for coming over.
-No problem.
Ooh! You made little sandwiches!
Yeah, that's cucumber
and cream cheese.
That's turkey and loganberry.
And don't tell my hips, but I'm
warming up a brie in the oven.
Nice. So...
What's up?
Okay, well, I've been reading up
on all the side effects
you can get from estrogen, and...
I need you to be honest with me.
Do my boobs look bigger to you?
Well, it's kind of hard to tell.
Come on, Raj,
it's a "yes or no" question.
I'm not sure. Um... Wait.
Jump up and down,
let's see if they jiggle.
No, I... I still can't tell. Uh...
Oh, you know what?
Okay, give me some of this.
-Seriously?
-Do you want my help or not?
Fine.
Okay, yup.
See, see, that looks like...
that looks like they could be bigger.
But, you know, I bet-- I bet when
I do it, mine do the same thing.
-Yeah, they kind of do.
-Hm... Let me see something.
Hey, easy!
-My nipples are sensitive.
-Oh. Sorry, sorry.
(EXHALES)
Okay.
I mean...
Yeah, maybe.
Okay, let me feel.
No, I am definitely up a cup size.
You know, but they're very firm,
so you've got that going for you.
-You think?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, very perky.
Thank you.
I really needed to hear that today.
(OVEN DINGS)
-Ooh! Brie's ready!
-Yay!
-Good morning.
-Hello.
So am I driving you to work,
or are you still mad at me?
I'd like a ride.
Assuming you actually do
take me to work.
Where do you think I would take you?
Who knows? You said
you'd be home yesterday,
but you came home three days ago.
You say you're taking me
to work, but for all I know,
I'll end up
in a deserted amusement park.
Or a cornfield maze.
Or a back-alley dog fight.
You tell me.
I'm going to work.
You can come if you want.
Okay.
By the way, you have
something on your shirt.
-No, I don't.
-Hurts, doesn't it?
You know, I find myself wondering
if anything you've
ever told me is true.
I didn't make it back.
The ship sank, I'm in hell.
You say you're from New Jersey,
but how can I believe you?
Why would anyone claim to be
from New Jersey if they weren't?
All right, I'll give you that one.
Hey, I said I was sorry.
What else do you want from me?
I want you to admit that
what you did was wrong.
Fine. What I did was wrong.
I wish I could believe you.
You know what?
I'm not driving you to work,
because you're incredibly annoying.
You say one thing and do the other,
so then you are driving me
and you find me a delight.
-Stop it.
-Keep it up?
-Bye!
-Hello!
So I guess you're really
holding up the other four fingers?
Oh, hey, what are you
doing here so early?
-Driving Sheldon to work.
-He's still mad at Leonard, huh?
He's mad at you, too.
He says you're the succubus
who led his friend astray.
I don't know
what "succubus” is, but...
it has "suck" in it,
so that can't be good.
-Thought I heard you out here.
-Hey, Sheldon.
You don't get a "hey."
You get a "hmm."
Come on, don't be like that.
We had so much fun together
the last couple of months.
You're right. Which makes your
betrayal all the more devastating.
-Sheldon...
- I let you buy
feminine hygiene products
with my supermarket club card.
You have any idea the kind of coupons
I'm going to get in the mail now?
Sheldon, your fight's with Leonard.
Penny's got nothing to do--
Careful, Amy.
The friend of my enemy'’s girlfriend
is my enemy.
-Really?
-Yes.
You're either with me or against me.
You want to take the bus to work?
Maybe there's a third option.
FYI, I had a doughnut
for breakfast, you jerk.
So now we're just waiting
for the data
from the ship to be crunched, but the
numbers look pretty promising.
That's so great. If you guys prove
the existence of Unruh radiation--
Hey, hey, hey!
My eyes are up here.
Howard, Raj, Judas.
You know what?
You're a crazy person.
A crazy person with a long memory,
and if all goes according to plan,
a robot army.
-Stop it.
-Or a mutant army.
It depends on how
my Kick starter goes.
I said stop it!
Now, listen to me.
You two aren't just friends.
You're best friends.
And that's a beautiful thing.
I mean, Leonard, you know
why he's so mad at you?
It's 'cause he missed you!
Yeah, and as his friend,
you should be happy
he has love in his life.
As I do.
This man held my breast
the other day, and I love him for it.
A little loud, dude.
So can we please put aside
these petty differences
and just be glad
we're here together?
-Okay.
- I suppose so.
Thank you.
It wasn't anything weird.
It was just to see how big they were.
And then Leonard took me
to the barber and the dentist,
and then to cap off the perfect day,
the Los Angeles Bureau
of Weights and Measures.
I thought the measures were
going to be the stars of the show.
Turns out it was the weights.
I'm so glad you guys
are friends again.
And I'm glad you and I
are friends again, too.
Which reminds me. This came in the
mail, and I want you to have it.
"Fifty cents off Vagisil."
Think of me when you apply it.
Can I just say, I've missed
all of us hanging out together.
-Yeah.
-Me, too.
Um, since when can Koothrappali talk
in front of the girls without a beer?
Oh, that happened
right after you left.
And no one told me?
Can't believe we forgot to tell him.
Ahem. Think of Sheldon
when you apply it.
(English - US SDH)